I'm going to share with you how Close3D is used in our clothing professional class system.
So my topic is how Close3D is used in clothing professional class system reform.
It is mainly divided into five aspects.
The first is to talk about the introduction of our school.
This introduction is based on why this course was introduced,
and why this software was introduced.
The second is the background of our professional class system reform.
The third is to talk about how our school is exploring the reform of clothing professional,
which is two professions, clothing and clothing design,
as well as clothing design and engineering.
How to explore the reform of this class system.
The fourth is to choose some cases in the course,
and then share with you how we use Close3D.
The fifth is to talk about the next steps
to think about how to further implement the reform of the class system.
Next, I will first talk about our school.
Our school is a public art school.
It mainly focuses on design.
Its characteristics are public art and design.
So our class, our clothing school,
in order to integrate with our school's concept,
we mainly emphasize one thing, that is, clothing.
We mainly emphasize one thing, that is, clothing.
This is the concept of innovation and implementation.
At the same time, we introduced a class system to traditional German.
We integrated a series of classes involving traditional clothing culture,
traditional clothing craftsmanship,
the pattern, the cultural patterns,
clothing history, etc.
These have been included in the course model.
into a special course module.
So, the main focus of our training is
the creative application design talent goal
of science, humanities, art, and practice.
The purpose of this introduction
is to explain how to implement
this talent goal
in our courses.
Because our school's
class reform of the department of clothing
started in 2017.
It was based on the digital transformation of the fashion industry.
The direction of clothing development
is also in the direction of intelligent, functional, and digital development.
So, when I was studying in Donghua University,
we considered to promote this thing in 2010.
I think it was Close 3D.
It was announced in Donghua University.
After listening to the speech,
I found that this might be the direction of our future.
So, I started to prepare for this thing at that time.
But it may not have started to develop in China at that time.
And Close 3D was still in use at that time.
Then there is also my personal experience and direction of research.
Because I also do functional clothing
and digital fashion.
This is a combination of research directions.
So, I think
my research results and other ideas
are integrated into my professional construction.
In 2016,
we proposed the construction of this digital lab.
In 2019, with the support of Close 3D,
and the information of Shanghai,
we built our clothing digital lab.
We introduced our Close 3D software.
And also,
we gradually introduced a system of 3D human-to-human scanning.
we introduced a fabric scanning machine.
It was introduced in 2020.
In 2022, we basically completed a human-to-human measurement.
We constructed 3D models,
and also made clothing,
fabric scanning,
and the production of fabric-based fabrics.
We adjusted the clothing pattern.
And finally,
we showed the interaction operation.
We showed the whole process of the clothing design
of the fabric-based clothing.
But now,
we still need a system
for testing the physical performance of the fabric.
Because now,
after scanning the fabric,
it only obtains a shape and a three-dimensional shape.
But the physical performance of the fabric,
we are still
trying to find other ways to process it.
But now, there is a problem that does not match.
So, this problem has not been solved yet.
We are also preparing to solve this problem in the next year or two.
So, we built a lab.
And then, based on this fabric-based lab,
we, the clothing professional course system,
will carry out some reformed explorations.
First of all, when we first started,
it was a single-door course to a course system.
This morning, I used a single-door course.
It is a course that I taught myself.
It is called Clothing Design Technology.
It was in 2020.
Because our software was just introduced.
It was first introduced in 2019.
So, we started using it in this course.
But at that time,
it was still just a single-door course.
It was a single-door course.
Then, we gradually expanded to many courses.
I will talk about it later.
The second problem is that our software
is simply a showcase of software technology.
It is a application of technology.
And then, it combines some of our courses
to do some product development.
The third problem is that since last year,
we have been exploring a fusion of
Closed 3D software and other software.
So, we have changed from a single-door Closed 3D software
to a fusion of Closed 3D and Blender software.
This is our exploration.
Next, I would like to talk about
the course of our human development program.
At the earliest, our course was only
based on the Closed 3D technology that I mentioned earlier.
We went to the traditional floating board structure.
That is, at that time, we did some of the things
that were hot in the past two years.
It is a return to traditional floating.
In 2022, after 30 years,
we will be like what Mr. Gao said just now.
For example, our Closed 3D Closed 3D class
is also inspired by Closed 3D.
Because in the past, the Closed 3D
was a flat structure explanation.
The students may not understand
what the flat form of the Closed 3D is like.
It is impossible to form this kind of three-dimensional transformation process.
Including our Closed 3D 1 and 2,
the course of the four kinds of 3D
are all like this.
There is no such thing.
In addition, from 2002,
we have launched a course called
Fuzhang Three-dimensional virtual representation.
This class is purely a course of the
3D technology of our two Closed 3D.
It is a course on a course of teaching
from the basics to almost a complete state.
Then we will show
I took this class in the department of clothing and human resources and engineering.
We have been using this product in clothing and human resources and engineering since the introduction of the channel.
We have also used this software in the design of clothes.
Since last year, students have been using this software in the design of clothes and research papers.
We have also used this software in the design of clothing and human resources and engineering.
In our course, teachers will use this software in the design of clothes and human resources and engineering.
So this is how we form a course system.
In fact, according to what Mr. Gao said just now,
I think we can continue to integrate it into the course of traditional German class groups.
For example, in terms of patterns and colors,
including materials and so on,
we can use this software to introduce this course 3D software.
This is a reform of our course system.
Next, I will talk about the case.
The first case is the course of clothing and human resources and engineering.
It is actually a training of software technology.
Here we start from the basics.
We will have a class of clothes,
we will have a class of shirts,
we will have a class of pants and trousers.
This is the basic form of the course.
During the second half of the class,
we will have students do some expansion in the design of clothes.
We will have students do some expansion in the design of clothes.
and then do some structural design,
and then show it in three-dimensional form.
These are some of the students' homework.
This is a basic training course on software technology.
We usually design this course in the first year of primary school.
We took this course quite early.
Why did we take this course so early?
It's mainly to help students master software technology even earlier.
Because students used to use PS and AI software before.
If they learn it on their own, they can do it pretty fast.
We usually let them learn on their own in the early and mid-level courses.
We also talk about it in the classroom.
After we talk about it, they will continue the course.
After the class,
they will start to learn on their own.
So this is the only course we specifically set up for the students.
The rest of the courses are done by the students themselves.
Because we mainly want to train the students to learn on their own.
The second course is the course on software technology.
In my course,
I talked about how we relied on one of our students last year.
The session was a series of courses done by the Ministry of Education.
One of our courses is to design a three-dimensional human scan method.
And then we will collect this data model,
which is what we called the model that we will display.
This model has been collected from three-dimensional human scan.
Of course, our school has a numerical school.
So we used the digital academy to let them process the model for us.
Then we made the model like this.
So our course is actually combined with another professional of the academy.
They also do 3D animation.
So the digital academy has the conditions to cooperate with us.
As for this model, we need to perform the CD drawing version.
The basic version, that is, the round shape.
This round shape, of course, we first learned how to make this round shape in the course.
Then we put it in our human body to carry out the basic version to see if it is suitable.
We need to adjust this process, a verification process.
Then after verification, we need to carry out the customized design plan.
Because this course is a one-on-one customized, so we made a customized plan.
After the customized plan is designed, we need to let the students choose.
We need to get the material and the digital material.
This is just right, because we have the material scanner.
So we let the students go to purchase the material.
Then use the material sample machine to scan what it is.
First of all, it is to get some of the material that we are talking about.
Some of its appearance, after we scan it, it will form a format of several files.
One is a line drawing, etc.
So we can make the material in a three-dimensional form.
Then we will analyze the material with some physical parameters.
We use another machine to measure it, so it is still different from the machine equipped with the cloth.
But we have no way to do this.
Now we can only say as a general data reference.
Then we went to this CD edition.
After the edition, we started the costume, digital costume production process.
After the production of this digital costume, we will teach them how to use this Blender to make the main show video with the digital school.
Then we will make the main show video with the digital school.
This is a virtual show of embroidery.
We did this course last year,
and it was quite long.
Although we only had 40 courses,
we basically used more than one semester.
This is the costume that the students wore after the show.
We had a theme for the show,
which was a coat in autumn and winter.
Autumn and winter coats.
So we designed this costume
based on the materials that the students chose.
Of course, the theme that we chose was a pinstripe.
This pinstripe can be a color pinstripe,
or it can be a pinstripe of different materials.
So this is a pinstripe theme that we chose.
This theme is placed relatively large,
so the students can have a free space to express themselves.
This is a technical application of our course.
Later, I have a video
that talks about the fusion of clothes and blenders.
I put the link in the back
and I will show it to you later.
This is a technical application of our course.
We also have the costume paper pattern class that we just talked about.
In our costume paper pattern class,
because the teacher
made all the basic styles
in the previous period.
The purpose of this is to let the students understand
the flat paper pattern and the three-dimensional pattern,
the three-dimensional pattern and the three-dimensional pattern.
The cost of applying the two-dimensional pattern
is the same as the flat paper pattern.
You can use this to build a relationship
between this two types of patterns.
As I'm talking about the costume paper pattern 1,
from the round shape to the pattern of the shoes,
the round shape to the pattern of the ball,
to the many other patterns,
to the round shape et cetera,
and to the round shape.
The students can understand
the basic relationship between
the two-dimensional pattern of the costume
and the shape.
So they will understand the principle of this structure.
We applied the traditional Fuzi board structure.
Of course, I didn't teach this class.
It was taught by another teacher at our school,
Mr. Fan Chonghong.
In this class, we also did a kind of restoration.
But this restoration was done in 2001.
It wasn't that perfect.
So we also asked the students to get the board structure
and get the data of the board structure.
Then we made the sample board.
After making the sample board, we also tried it out.
At the same time, we also turned the pattern of the pattern
into a death pattern through AI.
Then we melted it into our fabric.
This is how we realized the traditional Fuzi board structure.
It's a board structure
and a reconstruction of a similar structure.
It can only be called a reconstruction of a structure.
If we want to make a complete reconstruction,
we may not be able to do it.
Because of the fabric,
we may not be able to achieve this yet.
How can we get this state that is closer to the death pattern?
We also introduced this class
to this kind of design competition and innovation project.
For example, we have a lot of students applying every year.
Everyone is innovative.
There are hundreds of them.
So this is an innovation project.
Many of these innovation projects
combine this kind of,
the new digitalization technology,
such as the Macro 3D software.
This is the survival show concept that our students made.
This is an innovation design part.
These students did it relatively well.
So I took it as an example.
They used a lot of traditional things like Shandong here.
Traditional craftsmanship and like hardware.
Like hand-madeitas,
like hand-madeitas,
as well as the pattern of Lu Jing and some embroidery.
So this is a re-design application of a fashion designer
that combines the modern style.
This student made a three-door handkerchief.
He combined the pattern of Lu Jing and the image of San Haijin.
He made a three-door handkerchief.
This is a three-dimensional digital re-design of the Chinese fashion designer Tang Feng
that we organized last year.
This is a student's work.
I participated in the guidance process.
I found that the three-dimensional digital re-design of the traditional fashion
is the same as the previous one.
I found that the three-dimensional digital re-design of the traditional fashion is the same as the previous one.
This is because I participated in the competition.
So from the level of delicacy of the model and the level of delicacy of the fabric,
as well as the details of the painting,
I have made a lot of progress.
I have also received a lot of inspiration.
I think this competition is good.
We can continue to participate in this kind of competition in the next step.
Although the students have not won the award this time,
there are two works that have been nominated.
There is also one that we made with the company last year.
It is a company in Tai'an.
It is specialized in functional clothing, which is a motorbike suit.
They want to develop a children's dragonfly suit.
Based on this, we cooperated with them to design a children's dragonfly suit.
Because it includes super large items,
the apply the influence of traditional cultural elements,
and a lot of concept designs,
the자가 protection protection
So, the design of what we note
does not have as much freedom as the other fashion designs we like.
There is a language barrier.
So, I am planning to give class called the Cl dissect répon mainland fashion design.
In my course, I focused on the results of the college student innovation project as the goal of the course.
That is to say, each student has to announce the college student innovation project in this course.
Each student has to choose a theme to do it.
This is a student who just graduated last year.
He did a design of a yoga suit in the Department of Humanities and Engineering.
He did a high-temperature yoga suit.
Then he used Cross3D to simulate the shape and the dynamic,
the static-magnetic shape to do this kind of verification and adjustment.
His project was quite successful.
We even did an experiment later.
And he is now writing a paper on it.
It may be published in a nuclear magazine.
This is the adult cognitive technology course I just talked about.
We put this Cross3D,
which is not a combination of a single software and other software,
into this course.
I will play this video for you.
I will play it for you.
The time is limited.
At that time, we were doing digital male students.
Digital male students.
That is to say, there were online models in the online course.
They were also in the course.
Of course, this Blender animation was made.
We made this Blender animation a little bit more abstract.
Because the students just mastered this.
The technology.
So it's not very good.
Because the other one.
We were trying to show this time.
It's a bit tight.
Because many of them are made by students.
It's time-consuming.
So I'm not in this one.
I'm not in that one.
I'll let him go.
Because the time is limited.
So I'll show you this quickly.
Through such an exhibition process,
you can understand the comparison between the exhibition in the digital world and the exhibition in the real world.
This is a comparison.
This is a practice of our custom class.
And then at the end, I want to talk about it.
It's a world of thinking about the reform of our cultural and political science course system.
The first one.
Actually, I think Mr. Gao did a good job just now.
They made a resource library.
That's what we want to do.
How to use this 3D technology to improve the efficiency of teaching.
Because now we.
I feel that a lot of this information we used to have is hard to keep.
With this 3D technology,
how to achieve this is to form this.
This is what we call our own database.
But I don't think this kind of free database is enough.
Far from enough.
I want to be like this.
Like this kind of mobile app ecosystem.
So how to make it a big ecosystem.
Let everyone be able to share all of us.
This is some of the information we had before.
Or this is the kind of model we made.
And some of the information we taught.
This is how to form a sharing platform.
This will greatly improve the efficiency of our teaching.
The second one.
I think what I want to do is.
It's also what I tried before.
It's close 3D.
It can be combined with some other digital software like Blender.
This kind of software.
That can realize our virtual dynamic display.
It can also apply this kind of video scene integration.
This may be the next step.
Like this.
Shara.
Like this artificial intelligence.
Maybe we can combine this model.
So we can realize.
We don't need this model.
Like now.
You still need a model to film this.
To show our final product.
Then we may be completely through this virtual software.
Will realize this kind of static and dynamic.
This kind of various displays.
You can even integrate the scene.
Of course, in fact, we have a lot of this kind of clothing.
In this kind of display.
In this kind of flat broadcast.
Already used this kind of.
This kind of scene called AI.
And we are this kind of.
This kind of shooting of clothing.
This kind of fusion.
The third one.
I think our course is.
How to do this in the future.
With AIGX.
This artificial intelligence model.
I'm using this AIGX here.
Because it's.
It may be generated content.
It may also be generated this kind of picture.
Can generate videos and so on.
You say this kind of fusion.
It may also be a trend in our future.
This is the future.
This kind of intelligent design.
Like Mr. Gao just said.
It's about this.
It's artificial intelligence.
We may bring us.
We.
I think this thing.
I am very.
This kind of positive attitude.
I think this artificial intelligence.
Brought to us.
This kind of student.
Their kind of design.
This kind of efficiency.
The ability to design.
Will greatly improve.
Especially for us.
This engineering student.
Because our engineering student.
He is not like the previous design student.
His kind of painting.
Painting skills.
It's relatively weak.
That's just right.
Our artificial intelligence.
He made up for this skill.
Such a.
Training.
Learning process.
Then we.
This community only needs.
In the age of artificial intelligence.
It may be mainly.
Spread to students.
More importantly.
Is a kind of design thinking.
And design methods.
Including us.
This class.
I am now.
Our class is also like this.
It's mainly.
Put in the students.
This kind of method.
And the improvement of ability.
So.
Knowledge.
This piece.
We more.
Let students learn by themselves.
And then.
In the course.
Is to let students.
To use a way of exploring themselves.
The teacher.
Is to guide him.
How to learn.
That.
My own learning process.
All done by students.
Like we just talked about.
That.
Artificial intelligence engineering.
And artificial intelligence technology.
These courses.
We.
Are guided by the project.
And.
This form.
Whether it's a business project.
Or this kind of.
It's.
Everything that has passed.
Also we.
We've been doing it.
And what we're doing here.
In a lot of things.
Not enough.
Especially like our.
Just now.
Mr. Gao.
Can do very detail.
We've got.
Perhaps a little bit thick.
I'm talking so much today.
You don't have time.
Thank you.
All right.
Good voilà.
Thank you.
You also have a first.
To I.
Thank you, buddy.
And how do people think the.
You know.
Let's.